- 잘잤어?
- 와!
- Morning, roomie.
- Hey!
나 있다고
옷입고 나왔네?
You remembered
to put clothes on this morning.
운이 좋았어
Fifth day's a charm.
조이, 돌아오니까 참 좋다
네 덕분에 나랑 엠마 아주 편안해
It's so great to be back here. You're
making it so easy on me and Emma.
네가 돌아오니까 나도 좋아
있고 싶을 때까지 있어
It's great having you back.
Stay as long as you want.
그나저나 엠마 밤새 우는건
언제쯤 나아질까?
And when does she stop
crying all night?
야! 옷입고 있네!
Hey! You're not naked.
오늘 저녁
몇시에 데리러 올거야?
Rach, when will we expect
to see you tonight?
여섯시쯤에 엠마 데리러 갈게
엠마 준비 다 해놨는데
Probably around 6. But she's
in the bedroom, all ready to go.
지금 또 잠들었어
But she fell back to sleep, so..
밤새도록 사랑스럽게
울어댔기 때문에 피곤할거야
She's probably exhausted from all that
adorable screaming she did last night.
- 안녕
- 잘가
- Bye.
엠마 때문에 네가 너무
힘든거 아닌지 모르겠다
Hey, I hope Emma isn't
making it too hard on you.
- 천만에! 아주 좋아!
- 그래?
No, hey, it's been great.
레이첼 여기 있는거 걱정마
I just want you to know that
with Rachel staying here..
나 지난 감정 다 정리했어
all my feelings from before
are totally over.
설사 감정이 있다고 해도
And even if they weren't..
일단 여자가
유축기 쓰는걸 보면..
when you walk in on a woman
using a breast pump..
- 그래, 확 깨지
- 으!
- Yeah, that'll do it.
- Wow!
넌 어때?
So how are you?
- 괜찮아
- 정말?
- I'm okay.
- Really?
그럼, 레이첼과 잘됐으면
물론 더없이 좋았겠지
Sure. I mean, do I wish me and Rachel
living together would have worked out?
실망스럽긴 하지만
이혼한 것도 아니잖아
Of course. You know, I'm disappointed,
but it's not like it's a divorce.
- 그래도 사실상..
- 아냐! 이건 결코 이혼이 아냐!
- Well, actually it..
- It's not a divorce. It is not a divorce!
레이첼도 나도 각자의 인생을
살아야 한다고 생각해
Anyway, I think Rachel and I
need to get on with our lives.
우선 사람들부터 만날거야
Maybe start seeing other people.
와, 진짜?
Wow. Really?
그래, 안될것 없잖아? 나한테
소개해 줄만한 좋은 여자 없니?
Sure, why not? In fact, if you know
anyone that'd be good for me..?
- 여자들이야 많이 알지
- 떠오르는 이름 없어?
- Sure. I know lots of girls.
- Any names come to mind?
이름씩이나?
Names?
프렌즈 시즌 9
'소개팅'
뭐 먹을 참이었는데
너도 먹을래?
- I was about to eat. Want something?
- What you got?
메뉴가 뭔데?
콩 이유식, 당근 이유식..
Okay, let's see, we got strained peas,
strained carrots..
자두 이유식이 있네!
아직 안먹어 본거야!
strained plums.
We haven't tried that yet!
좋아!
Goody!
고마워
Thanks.
레이첼이랑 다시
같이 사니까 어때?
So how is it living with Rachel again?
음식 좋아진건 빼고 말야
I mean, apart from the great food?
난 괜찮아
그런데..
I'm fine, I'm fine. It's just..
로스랑 레이첼은
왜 그러는지 모르겠어
It's just weird what's happening
with her and Ross.
어젠 로스가 여자를
소개시켜 달라고 하더라구
Yesterday he asked me to fix him up
with somebody.
어쩜! 레이첼도 나한테
남자를 소개시켜 달랬어!
Rachel asked me
if I knew anyone for her too.
- 둘이 대체 왜 그런대?
- 그러게 말야
- Why are they doing this?
- I don't know.
서로 천생연분인데 말야
아무튼 미쳤어
They're so perfect for each other.
It's crazy.
진짜 미치겠다!
You know what's crazy? These jars.
이게 뭐야!
두입 먹으면 땡이잖아!
What is there, like, two bites in here?
둘이 서로가 좋은 짝이란걸
깨달았으면 좋겠어
I just wish they'd realize
they should be together.
맞아, 둘이 같이 산다고 했을때
이제야 제대로 되는구나 했는데
When they moved in together, I figured
that's where things were headed.
맞아, 걔넨 가정을 이뤄야해
결혼해서 아이들도 더 낳고
They should be a family. They should
marry and have more children.
그리고 애들중 한명은
조이라고 이름 붙여야해
Yes. And they should name
one of their kids Joey.
난 애가 없을지도 모르는데
누군간 내 성을 물려받아야지
I may not have kids. Someone's
gotta carry on the family name.
그거 알아?
둘다 다른사람 만나보면
You know what? Maybe once they
start dating and see what's out there..
서로가 얼마나 소중한지
깨닫게 될거야
they'll realize how good
they are for each other.
- 맞아, 골라봤자라니까
- 그래
Yeah, because it is slim pickings.
어제 여자를 만났는데
너무 꽝이야!
I had this date last night. Yuck!
크게 얘기하지마
아직 안에서 자고 있거든
But we should probably keep it down,
she's still in the bedroom.
어떡하지? 걔들한테
딴사람 소개시켜줘야 해?
So, what are we gonna do? Are we
just gonna set them up with people?
- 둘사이는 더 멀어질텐데?
- 맞아
I know, that just pushes them
further and further apart.
이렇게 하면 되겠다
I know what we can do. We could set
Ross and Rachel up on horrible dates..
로스와 레이첼에게
끔찍한 사람들을 소개시키는 거야
그럼 서로가 얼마나 잘맞는
커플인지 깨닫게 말야
so they'll realize
how good they are together.
- 그거 멋진 계획이다!
- 그렇지?
- That's a great plan.
- Yeah.
제일 멋진건 음모를 꾸민
악당처럼 웃을수 있다는 거야
You know what the best part of it is?
I get to do my plan laugh.
쉿, 저 여자 깨겠다
이름이 뭐더라?
Okay, shh! Not so loud.
We don't want to wake up..
안녕.. 두사람
오늘 저녁 별일 없지?
Hi. You guys aren't
doing anything tonight, are you?
왜 그럴거라고 생각하지?
우리가 결혼해서?
See, now, why would you assume that?
Just because we're married?
우리가 얼마나
바쁜 신세대 부부인지 모르는군
I mean, I will have you know that
we are very hip, happening people.
미안하지만 난 읽던 부고란
다시 읽어야겠어
Now if you'll excuse me, I have to
get back to reading the obituaries.
오늘 저녁에 엠마 봐줄수
있는지 물어본것 뿐이야
I was just asking because I need
someone to watch Emma tonight.
그래, 봐줄께
무슨 일이야?
Sure we'll do it.
What are you up to?
- 피비가 남자 소개시켜준대
- 어머!
- Well, Phoebe set me up on a date.
- Oh, my God.
- 왜? 뭐 어때서?
- 난 너와 오빠가..
- Why? What's the big deal?
- I figured because you and Ross are..
1년 반전에 함께 잤다구?
난 준비됐어
What? Slept together a year
and a half ago? Yeah, I'm all set.
새로운 남자 만나는건
아주 잘하는것 같아
I think it's great you're going on a date.
It sounds healthy.
건강한 일이라구!
네 여성성을 만끽해!
I mean, you have needs.
Embrace your womanhood.
취직하고 싶어? 그럼 오프라 쇼
그만 보고 이력서나 보내!
You want a job? Turn off Oprah
and send out a resume.
- 엠마 일곱시쯤 데리고 올게, 괜찮지?
- 괜찮구말구
- I'll bring her by around 7, okay?
- That's perfect.
시간가는 줄 모를 거야!
한창 예쁜짓 할때거든
You guys are gonna have so much fun.
She's at such a cute age.
요즘 고형식을 먹기 때문에
한시간 간격으로 응가 할거야
A couple things. Now that she eats
solid food, she poops around the clock.
머리카락 조심해
엠마가 잘 잡아당기거든
And watch out for your hair
because she likes to grab it.
그리고 방에 사람이 없으면
목이 터져라 울거야
She's also in this phase where if you
leave the room, she screams, but..
어째든 고마워
재미있게 보내
Thanks, you guys. Have fun.
갑자기 부고란에서
내 이름을 보고 싶어진다
Suddenly I wish I was reading
my own name.
조이? 오늘 레이첼한테
Joey, hey. I'm so excited.
- 끔직한 남자 소개시켜주기로 했어
- 그래? 누군데?
- I set Rachel up with the worst guy.
- All right. Who is he?
내 마사지 고객이었는데
It's a guy I used to massage.
By "massage"..
툭하면 돌아누워 자기 물건
자랑하려고 해서 막느라고 힘들었어
I mean hold down so he wouldn't
turn over and flash me.
내가 고른 로스 상대도
아주 끔찍해
- Wait till you hear who I got for Ross.
- Oh, yeah.
얘기해봐!
진짜 따분한 여자야
학교 선생님이래!
Okay. She's this really boring woman.
She's a teacher.
선생님?
- A teacher?
- She's into history and foreign movies.
또 역사와 외국영화에
관심이 무지 많더라구!
그리고 퍼즐도 좋아한대!
And she loves puzzles.
퍼즐 좋아하는 사람도 있냐?
Come on, who loves puzzles?
로스가 좋아하잖아!
Well, Ross does.
너 때문에 우리 계획 망치겠어!
You're ruining the plan!
로스에게 이상형을
붙여주는 셈이잖아!
Joey, you fixed him up
with his perfect woman.
맙소사! 그렇구나!
- Oh, my God, you're right!
- Yeah.
그 여자 독서가 취미랬어!
어떡하지?
She even reads for pleasure!
그런데 네가 그런 여자를
어떻게 알아?
- How do you know a woman like that?
- I'm not allowed to know smart women?
뭐? 난 똑똑한 여자를
만날리가 없다는 거야?
조이?
- Joey?
- We met at the library. I went in to pee.
화장실 급해서
도서관에 갔다가 만났어
- 이제 어떡하지?
- 그 여자한테
- So now what do we do?
- Well, okay.
소개팅 취소됐다고 하고
딴 여자 구해야지
I'll call her and tell her the date's
canceled and find him somebody else.
딴 여자 구할것 없어
그 여자한테는 취소됐다고 하고
What if we don't find him somebody
else? We'll just tell her the date's off..
로스한테는 아무말 안하는 거야
그럼 로스 혼자 바람맞는 거잖아
but we don't tell Ross. He'll go
to the restaurant and get stood up.
야! 그거 좋겠다!
I hear that's bad.
정말 잘됐다!
레이첼은 끔찍한 남자를 만나고
So this is great. Rachel's
gonna have a terrible date..
로스는 바람을 맞는거야, 그러면
둘은 서로의 소중함을 깨닫겠지
Ross gets stood up, and then they'll
realize how good they have it together.
그래, 멋진 음모다!
Yes, the plan.
그건 산타할아버지 웃음이지!
It's not Santa's plan.
이렇게 해야지
No, it's..
- 별로 재미없다
- 제대로 못해서 그래
- Yeah, you know, it's not that fun.
- No, I think we killed it.
엠마? 여기좀 봐
Emma? Emma, look at me!
나 잠깐 아래층 갔다올게
Well, I think I'll go downstairs
for a while.
아냐, 울지마!
나 안갔어!
No, no, no! It's okay! It's okay!
I didn't go!
장난 친거야
Don't cry, it's just a bit!
이 챈들러 고모부는
원래 웃긴 사람이잖니!
I'm your Uncle Chandler.
Funny is all I have!
알지? 나 내일부터
6일까지 배란기야
Okay, just so you know, I'm gonna be
ovulating from tomorrow until the 6th.
앞으로 48시간 동안은
자기 몸에 손대지마!
So don't touch yourself
for the next 48 hours.
난 그런짓 안해
I don't do that.
알았어, 노력할게
I'll try to stop.
- 6일까지라고 했어?
- 그래
- Did you say until the 6th?
- Yeah.
오늘이 6일인데?
Today is the 6th.
아냐, 봐
No, it's not.
올해는 2003년이라구
Yes, it's also 2003.
어머!
오늘이 6일이야?
Oh, my God. Today's the 6th?
그럼 배란이 끝났을 지도 몰라!
I may be done ovulating!
오늘 손님한테 내놓은 고기
신선도도 의심스러워지는걸!
I may have also served some very
questionable meat at the restaurant.
- 가서 배란테스트 해봐
- 알았어
- Go take the test, see if we're okay.
- Okay.
쉽지 않네
Tough crib.
배란 테스트 막대 다 어디갔어?
하나밖에 없네
Hey, where are all my ovulation sticks?
There's only one here.
배란 중인지 궁금해서
내가 두어번 검사해봤어
I might have checked to see
if I was ovulating a couple times.
난 실직자야!
할일이 없단 말야!
I'm not working! There's not much
to do around here!
'델모니코스 레스토랑'
죄송해요, 빵도 드릴까요?
Sorry. You want a roll with that?
잠깐만요
Excuse me.
혹시 바에서 기다리는
여자분 없나요?
Is there a woman waiting at the bar?
키는 보통이고 갈색 머리에
퍼즐을 풀고 있을지 모르는데
Someone average height, dark hair?
Or perhaps doing a puzzle?
술취한 중국 남자 분밖에 없어요
There's a drunk Chinese guy.
내가 여기 한시간 이상 있으면
그분한테 술 한잔 사죠
Well, if I'm still here in an hour,
buy him a drink on me.
와인 한잔 더 갖다 드릴까요?
Can I get you another glass of wine?
안마실래요
이따가 취해있으면 곤란하거든요
I don't know if I should.
I don't want to be drunk when I..
이따가 혼자 집에 갈때..
go home alone tonight.
- 바람맞았나보죠?
- 괜찮아요, 소개팅이었거든요
- Got stood up, huh?
- It's no big deal. It's just a blind date.
여자가 손님을 보고 그냥
가버린게 아닐까 걱정되세요?
Are you worried your date came,
saw you and left?
아뇨!
No!
괜찮아!
나 아직 배란중이야!
We're okay. I'm still ovulating.
다행이다! 오늘 오후 4시까지
난 아니었거든
Oh, good, because as of 4:00
this afternoon, I am not.
빨리 하자
So let's do this.
- 지금은 안될것 같은데
- 자기가
- I don't think I can.
- Oh, come on.
18살 청춘 아닌건
알지만 안될건 없잖아
I know you're not 18 anymore,
but give it a minute.
- 엠마 때문에 말야
- 맞다, 엠마!
- Because of Emma.
- Oh, my God, Emma.
오, 네가 있는걸
깜박했구나!
Oh, sweetie, I forgot you were here.
할수 없네
엠마를 혼자 둘순 없어
You're right, we can't do this.
We can't leave her alone.
그래
Sorry.
하지만..
Unless..
여기서 하면 어떨까?
maybe we do it here.
이 꼬맹이가 알면 뭘
얼마나 알겠어?
I mean, how much can she even
be aware of at this age?
사람이 방을 나가면 금방 알고
울어대는 애 앞에서..
She's aware when we leave a room.
She may notice if we start..
부비적 거리면 알지 몰라
canoodling in it.
- 부비적?
- 아-기 앞에서
- Canoodling?
- Well, I can't say hump or screw..
섹스란 말을 어떻게 해!
in front of the B-A-B-Y.
글쎄, 난 애 앞에서
아기 만드는게
I don't know,
I guess having sex in front of a baby..
- 그렇게까지..
- 끔찍하지 않다구?
- isn't so..
- Horrifying? Scarring?
소름끼치지 않아?
감옥에 갈일은 아니라구?
Something people go to jail for?
- 자기 말이 맞는것 같아
- 맞는것 같아?
- I guess you're right.
- You guess?
여행 갔을때 창문으로 사슴이
At that bed-and-breakfast,
we didn't have sex..
쳐다보는것 같다고 도저히
못하겠다고 했던 사람이 누군데?
because you thought a deer
was staring through the window.
사슴 앞에서 그거하고
싶다면 변태 아냐?!
Well, what kind of a sick bastard
wants to do it in front of a deer?
와, 다 맛있어 보이네요
Wow, everything looks so good.
난 닭 요리 먹을래요
I think I'm gonna have the chicken.
이말 꼭 하고 싶군요
I just have to say this.
- 정말 아름다우세요
- 어머, 고마워요
- You're really beautiful.
- Wow, that's very sweet. Thank you.
난 웃기게 생겼죠?
I'm kind of funny-looking.
- 네?
- 알아요, 당신은 나한테
- What?
- Look, I mean, come on..
과분해요, 여기 사람들
다 그렇게 생각할걸요
you're way out of my league.
Everybody in here knows it.
"저 여자는 왜
저런 남자를 만나지?"
I bet that guy over there
is probably saying:
"남자가 부자인가 보군"
"Why's she out with him?
He must be rich."
하지만 난 부자도 아녜요
Well, I'm not.
그렇군요
Okay.
그럼, 저 남자만 무안하겠네요
Well, I guess, then the joke's on him.
뭐 주문할 거예요?
난 닭이 좋겠어요
What do you think you want to order?
I'm real excited about that chicken.
난 유머감각도 없어요
I'm not funny, either.
"얼굴은 별로지만
날 웃게 만들기는 하겠지"
So if you were thinking,
"Well, he's not that good-looking..
그렇게 생각한다면
그건 큰 착각이에요
but maybe we'll have some laughs,"
that ain't gonna happen.
억지로 웃는것도
웃는 거잖아요
Well, come on, Steve,
let's not rule out nervous laughter.
우리 빨리 주문해요
So, now, I think that we should order..
빨리 먹고 나가게요
and then eat, and then leave.
전 건강상 문제가 많아요
I have a lot of medical problems.
피비가 그러는데
Hey, now, wait a minute,
Phoebe told me..
식당을 운영한다구요?
멋진 일 같아요
that you owned your own restaurant.
That's impressive.
망했어요
마약 때문에
I lost it to drugs.
지금은 티셔츠에
그림 새겨 팔아요
I silk-screen T-shirts now.
정말요? 그일은 어때요?
Really? What's that like?
돈도 안생기는데 싫어하는 일을
한다는건 아주 보람있죠!
It's really fulfilling doing something
you hate for no money.
맞아요, 난 돈도 없고
재미도 없어요
That's right. I have no money,
I'm not funny..
코딱지 만한 원룸에
남자 둘과 함께 살구요
I live in a studio apartment
with two other guys.
게다가 거의 확실한
불임이에요
And I'm pretty sure I'm infertile.
오, 왜그래요, 스티브
Now, come on. Come on, Steve.
스스로에 대해 마음에 드는
부분이 분명히 있을 거예요
There must be something
that you like about yourself.
내 머리모양은
마음에 들어요
I do like my hair.
정말요?
Really?
'센트럴
퍼크'
- 여보세요?
- 피비, 나야!
- Hello?
- Phoebe, it's me!
너 잡히기만 해봐!
죽을줄 알아!
I'm going to hunt you down
and kill you.
안녕, 레이첼!
Hey, Rach!
이건 최악의 소개팅이야!
This is the worst date ever! How could
you set me up with this creep?
어떻게 저런 왕재수를
갖다 붙일수가 있어!
그사람은 내 친구라는걸 명심해
You know, you are talking about
one of my dear, dear friends.
상관없어!
이건 완전히 악몽이야!
I don't care. This guy is a nightmare.
그사람 약에 취하면 좀
맛이 가기는 해
All right, so he gets a little crazy
when he's stoned.
- 약 안먹었어!
- 담배 핀다고 나간적 없어?
- He's not stoned.
- Did he go out for a cigarette?
- 네번 나갔어
- 가엾은 레이첼!
- Yeah. Four times.
- My dear, sweet Rach.
계획대로 잘되고 있어
레이첼은 악몽 같은 시간을 보내고
Well, our plan is working.
Rachel's having a miserable time..
로스는 바람맞고 혼자 있겠지
and Ross is stood up somewhere
at a restaurant all alone.
잘됐다!
두사람 곧 다시 합칠거야!
Pretty soon they'll be back together.
우리가 한짓이 드러날 때쯤이면
우린 멕시코에 가 있겠지!
By the time anyone's figured out what
we've done, we'll be in sunny Mexico.
잠깐, 그건 다른 계획의
마지막 부분이구나!
Oh, wait, that's the end
of a different plan.
엠마 잠들었어
챈들러?
She's asleep. Chandler?
- 뭐하는 거야?
- 엠마도 이랬단 말야!
- What are you doing?
- Emma was doing it.
엠마 잠들었어
She's asleep.
- 오! 잠들었어? 그렇다면..
- 그래, 대신 빨리 끝내야해
- She's asleep. That means we can..
- Yes. But we have to be fast.
알았어, 노력할게
Oh, okay, I'll try.
- 자기는 소리 크게 내지마
- 알았어, 노력할게
- And you can't make any noise.
- Okay, I'll try.
아무도 없어?
Hello?
엠마?
Emma?
안녕?
Hey! Hi!
뭐하고 있니?
How are you? How are you?
고모랑 고모부는
어디 가구?
Where are your babysitters, huh?
침실 문은 왜 잠겨있지?
Why is the bedroom door closed?
아-기 보면서
섹-스 라니! 돌았어!
You can't have S-E-X
when you're taking care of a B-A-B-I-E.
안좋은 소식입니다
그 중국분 떠나셨어요
I've got bad news. The Chinese guy left.
인연이 아닌가보죠
If it was meant to be, it's meant to be.
바람맞긴 하셨지만
뭐 어떻습니까?
Look, you got stood up. Who cares?
저희가 좋은 시간 만들어 드리죠
편히 계세요
We're gonna show you a good time.
Sit and relax.
특별히 선물로
게살 케이크를 갖다 드리죠
In fact, let me bring you
a crab-cake appetizer on the house.
와! 무료라구요?
기분 좋은데요?
Wow, free crab cakes?
Well, that's nice.
오늘밤 여자와 함께
보내고 싶긴 했지만..
Although I was hoping
to have sex tonight.
게살 케이크면 돼요
Just the crab cakes.
저손님 계속 붙잡아두려구?
그건 반칙이야!
What are you doing? Are you trying
to get him to stay? You can't do that.
- 신경꺼!
- 무슨 일이죠?
- Just get out of here, okay?
- I'm sorry, what's going on?
웨이터끼리 내기를 했어요
Okay, the waiters have
a little pool going.
손님이 얼마나 오래 있다가
포기하고 집으로 가실지
We have a bet on how long it'll take
before you give up and go home.
뭐예요?!
What?!
남의 불행을 가지고
내기를 했단 말입니까?
You're making money off my misery?
9시 20분까지만 계시면
제가 돈을 땁니다
Well, if you stay till 9:20, I am.
이건 말도 안돼!
이렇게 모욕적인 일은 처음이에요!
This is unbelievable. I have never
been so insulted in my life.
집에 갈거니까 빨리
게살 케이크나 싸줘요!
Now, if you'll wrap up my free
crab cakes, I'll be on my way.
이상하네, 자기가 소리 지르고
내가 빨리 끝났어
Well, that was weird.
You were loud and I was fast.
이번엔 제대로 됐을것 같아
I think we may have
really done it this time.
빨리 임신테스트 해보고 싶어
I wish I didn't have to wait
to take a pregnancy test.
그것도 몇개 더 사놔야 할걸
You may want to get
some more of those too.
엠마 어디 있지?
Where's Emma?
맙소사! 엠마 어디 갔지?
엠마 어디 있어?!
Oh, my God, where's Emma?
Where's Emma?
나한테 묻지마!
난 자기랑 저안에 있었다구!
Don't ask me.
I was in there canoodling you.
레이첼이 일찍와서
데려갔나봐
Okay. Okay. I'm sure that Rachel
came home early and picked up Emma.
밖에 좀 찾아봐
난 레이첼한테 전화할게
You go look across the hall,
and I'll call her cell.
나 임신되게 해달라고 빌어!
You better hope we're pregnant..
엠마가 안되면 다른 아기라도
레이첼한테 돌려 줘야하니까!
because one way or another,
we're giving a baby back to Rachel!
내가 왜 당신 앞에서
우는지 모르겠어요!
I can't believe I'm crying
in front of you.
나 참 한심해 보이죠?
You must think I'm so pathetic.
아뇨, 난 울줄 아는 남자가
남자답다고 생각해요
No, no, no, I admire a man
who can cry.
- 정말요?
- 손대지 말아요!
- Really?
- Don't touch my coat.
미안해요
전화가 왔네요
Sorry, that's my phone.
- 여보세요?
- 레이첼, 잘돼가?
- Hello?
- Hey, Rach, how's it going?
내 평생 최악의 데이트야!
Oh, my God,
this is the worst date ever.
그만좀 해요!
Oh, come on.
그럼 우리가 잘될거라고
생각했어요?!
Look, you know what, I'm sorry, but did
you really think that this was going well?
- 무슨 일이야?
- 여기 들렀었니?
- What's up?
- Hey, did you stop by here?
- 아니
- 어떡해! 그렇다면..
- No.
- Oh, my God! Then..
오, 살았다!
엠마, 거기 있었구나!
Thank God! Emma, there you are!
뭐? 그게 무슨 소리야?
엠마가 어디 있었는데?
What? What do you mean,
"there you are"? Where was she?
아냐, 까꿍 놀이하고 있었어
호들갑 떨어야 엠마가 좋아하거든
We were playing peekaboo.
She loves it when I'm dramatic.
엠마를 왜 데려 간거야?
- Why the hell did you take her?
- Because you two were having sex!
너희 둘이 침실에서
뒹굴고 있었잖아!
- 우리 안그랬어!
- 거짓말하지마
- No, we weren't.
- Don't you lie to me.
챈들러 머리 보면 알아!
I can tell by Chandler's hair. You are
so lazy. Can't you get on top for once?
이 게으름뱅이!
또 네가 아래 누웠지?
그래, 맞아!
All right. All right, we were.
아기 가지려고 노력중이야
모니카 배란기라구
We're trying to make a baby.
Monica's ovulating.
다행이다! 오늘 오후 2시까지
난 아니었거든
Which is more than I can say for myself
as of 2:00 today.
너희들!
Guys!
배란테스트가 얼마나 비싼데
Seriously, those sticks
are expensive!
그렇다고 옆방에 엠마 혼자 두고
그러는건 용서되지 않아!
It's unacceptable that you'd have sex
with Emma in the next room.
레이첼한테 이를거야!
- I'll have to tell Rachel about this.
- Please don't. She will kill us.
- 안돼!
- 제발 말하지마, 조이!
우릴 가만 안둘거야
말할거야!
하지만 만약에..
Hey, I gotta. Unless..
만약에 뭐?
Unless what?
너희 첫째 아기 이름
조이라고 지으면 봐주지
Unless you name
your first-born child Joey.
- 뭐? 왜?
- 난 애가 없을지도 몰라!
- What? Why?
- Hey, I may never have kids..
누군가는 우리 집안 성을
이어받아야지!
and somebody's gotta
carry on my family name.
네 성은 트리비아니잖아!
Your family name is Tribbiani.
내가 속을줄 알았지?
You almost had me.
잠깐
Look..
뭐라고 대답할지
뻔히 알지만..
I think I know the answer
to this question, but..
나랑 같이 잘래요?
would you like to make love to me?
아뇨, 싫어요
Really, really not.
상관없어요
It's just as well.
어차피 난 안되니까
It doesn't work anyway.
반가웠어요
잘가요, 스티브
All right, well, that's good to know.
Good night, Steve.
- 왜그래?
- 지독한 저녁이었어
- Hey, what's wrong?
- I just had a rough night.
- 게살 케이크 먹을래?
- 윽!
Crab cake?
무슨 일인데?
Well, what happened?
자기한테 이런 얘기 하긴
뭣하지만..
This is kind of weird
to talk to you about this, but..
모니카가 그러는데
오늘 소개팅이었다며?
Monica told me you had a blind date.
- 그래
- 나도 했어
- Yeah.
- I did too.
그런데 한쪽이 나타나지 않아도
소개팅이라고 할수 있나?
But is it technically a date
if the other person doesn't show up?
저런! 여자가 널 보고 그냥
나가버린 걸까봐 그래?
Oh, no. Do you think she walked in,
saw you and left?
다들 왜그런 말을 하는거야?
Why does everyone keep saying that?
오늘 그남자야말로
안나왔으면 좋을 뻔했어
If it makes you feel any better,
I wish my date hadn't shown up.
- 그렇게 나빴어?
- 티셔츠 만들어서 먹고산다면서
- That bad?
- Well, he makes T-shirts for a living..
이걸 선물이랍시고
and he thought it would be
appropriate to give me..
주더라
this.
'FBI, 여자 신체 검사관'
FBI, 여자 신체 검사관?
"Female Body Inspector"?
사이즈가 몇이야?
What size is that?
그래서 첫째 아기이름
조이라고 지을거래?
Now wait a minute. So they're gonna
name their first child Joey?
어떻게 하면 둘째 이름을
피비라고 짓게 만들지?
How do I get them to name
the next one after me?
간단해, 그냥 걔네 침대에서
뒹굴때 쳐들어가
It's easy. You just
walk in on them having sex.
그럼 벌써 피비란 이름
셋은 벌어놨네!
Oh, so they owe me,
like, three Phoebes.
저것봐!
로스와 레이첼이야!
Oh, my God!
Look, it's Ross and Rachel!
계획대로 되고 있어!
The plan is working!
그거 그만해!
Don't do the plan laugh.
몇달만에 처음 한 데이트가
둘다 엉망이었네
The first dates we've had in months,
and they were both such disasters.
이상하지?
You know, it is weird..
피비는 나한테
끔찍한 남자를 소개시켜줬고
that Phoebe would set me up
on a date that was awful..
같은 날 조이가 너한테
소개한 여자는 바람을 맞췄잖아
on the same night Joey set you up
on a date that didn't even show.
잠깐!
Wait a minute.
걔들이 설마 일부러
그런건 아니겠지?
You don't think it was intentional?
그런 바보같은 짓을 하다니!
I mean, that's just stupid.
우린 천재야!
We're geniuses.
두사람 좀 봐
얘기가 잘 통하나봐
- Look at them! They're really bonding.
- They're falling in love all over again.
그래, 다시 사랑에 빠진거야!
어! 우리를 보고있어!
화난것 같은데?
Oh, they see us. Oh, they look mad.
알아챘나봐!
이쪽으로 오네! 튀어!
They figured it out.
They're coming. Run!
- 어디로?
- 멕시코!
- Where?
- Mexico!
아직도 안나타나네
Can you believe they're still not here?
글쎄 말야, 소개팅 하러 나왔는데
둘다 바람을 맞다니
I know. A double blind date
and we both get stood up.
별일이 다 있군
What are the chances?
정말 실망이다
I know, I'm so bummed.
공짜 게살 케이크
지금 줄래요?
Could we have
our free crab cakes now?
- 뭐라구요?
- 우리 바람맞았어요
- What?
- We've been stood up.
공짜 게살 케이크 주세요
And we want our free crab cakes.
당신은 어젯밤에
바람맞았잖아요
- You were stood up here last night.
- I know. It hurts.
맞아요, 마음이 아파요
이틀 연속으로 바람맞아서
게살 케이크 만한 멍이 생겼어요
Being stood up two nights in a row
has left a crab cake sized hole in my heart.
소용없습니다, 오늘 두분께
내기건 사람 아무도 없어요
Guys, give it a rest.
Nobody's betting on you tonight.
대신 저 남자가 언제 울음을
터뜨리느냐에 내기를 걸었죠
Although we do have a pool going
to see how long it takes that guy to cry.
내손은 너무 뚱뚱해!
I have such fat hands!
내 거시기가 싫어!
I hate my dick!